大家好，美丽的人们，在这段视频中，我们将结束对地点的讨论
Hello you beautiful people so in this video we're going to be finishing off our discussion of the locate
命令，特别是您将学习如何使用update dbe命令更新数据库。
command and in particular you're going to learn how to update the database using the update d be command.
在此过程中，您还将学习如何获得超级用户权限。
And you're also going to learn in the process how to gain super user privileges.
因此，使用sudo命令可以获得管理员权限。
So administrator privileges using the sudo command.
因此，这将是一场非常重要的讲座，不仅涉及到如何最大限度地利用
So this is going to be a very important lecture touching not only on how to make the most out of the
命令，但也为您提供了有关如何获得管理员权限的绝对信息
locate command but also giving you an absolute nugget of information on how to gain administrator privileges
这是一件非常有用的事情，能够在您的系统上做更多更高级别的事情。
which is such a useful thing to be able to do more higher level things on your system.
因此，在本视频结束时，您将了解如何在LOCATE命令使用时更新数据库。
So by the end of this video you're going to know how to update the database at the locate command uses.
因此，LOCATE命令始终为您提供准确和正确的结果，并且您还知道如何运行管理员
So the locate command always gives you accurate and correct results and you also know how to run administrator
使用sudo的命令。
commands using sudo.
所以这将是一场非常重要的讲座。
So this is going to be a very important lecture.
让我们直接跳进去吧。
Let's go ahead and jump right into it.
好的。
OK.
因此，让我们开始学习update D-B命令，它是update database Hebel name right的缩写。
So let's start learning about the update D-B command which is short for update database Hebel name right.
那么让我们在我们的桌面上创建一个新文件，然后移到我们的桌面，然后我们将创建一个新文件
So let's create a new file on our desktops and move to our desktop and we're going to create a new file
叫来找我XTi博士，这样我们就可以使用触摸命令找我Pontiac的T。
called Find me Dr. XTi so we can use the touch command find me Pontiac's T.
现在我们在桌面上有一个名为“查找活动”的文件。
And there we are we have a file called Finding activity on our desktop.
现在，如果我尝试运行LOCATE命令，因为此Find Me文件是在我们的数据库之前创建的
Now if I try and run the locate command because this find me file has been created before our database
已更新，如果我尝试定位，则LOCATE命令将无法在数据库中找到它
has been updated and the locate command won't be able to find it in the database if I try and locate
在这里找不到我。
find me not here.
我们看看是不是什么都拿不回来。
We'll see if we get absolutely nothing back.
好的。
OK.
即使文件存在，但它还没有输入到数据库中，因此它的位置
Even though the file exists it's not been entered into the database yet and therefore it the location
通过搜索数据库找不到它。
can't find it by searching the database.
好的。
OK.
所以要更新数据库都要添加到数据库中，我们需要更新数据库。
So to update the database were added to the database we need to update the database.
这就是UPDATE D-B Come命令的用武之地。
And that's where the update D-B come command comes in.
因此，如果我们尝试，它会注意到我们实际上收到了一个错误，错误表明shell无法打开
So if we try it will notice that we actually get an error and the error says that the shell cannot open
实际的数据库文件。
the actual database file.
原因是update D-B命令需要管理员权限才能运行
And the reason for that is the update D-B command requires administrator privileges in order to run
我们可以通过查看update D-B命令的手册页看到这一点，我们在
and we can see this by looking at the man page for the update D-B command and we see at the top of the
更新系统管理器部分中的D-B命令，该命令在手册的第8节中。
update D-B command that is in the system managers section it's in Section 8 of the manual.
这意味着它需要提升权限才能运行，您可以在这里看到我刚才所说的内容
And that means it requires elevated privileges in order to run and you can see here what I was saying
关于每天运行的更新D-B。
about Update D-B being run daily.
因此，如果你愿意，你可以阅读更多关于这方面的内容。
So you can read more about that if you like.
但这里重要的是，它在手册的第8节中，因此需要管理员
But the important thing here is that it's in Section 8 of the manual and therefore requires administrator
权限，以便运行并参考CHIHI关于手册结构的信息。
privileges in order to run and refer back to the Chichi about the manual structure.
如果您需要一点提示，以及手册的各个部分都做了些什么。
If that if you need a bit of reminder of that and what the sections of the manual do.
好的。
OK.
那么，我们如何才能获得管理权限才能运行此命令呢？
So how can we get the administrative privileges in order to run this command.
要做到这一点，您可以使用伪命令，我不确定它的发音是sudo还是su do，但发音是I吗？
Well to do that you use the pseudo command I'm not sure if it's pronounced sudo or su do but am I.
我喜欢寿司所以我们还是吃那个吧。
I like sudo so we'll stick with that.
因此，sudo命令非常简单，您只需在想要以管理员身份运行的任何命令之前编写它即可。
So the sudo command is very simple you just write it before any command you want to run as the administrator.
所以我要输入更新辩论，仅此而已。
So I'm going to type update debate and that's it.
好的。
OK.
现在，当我这样做时，因为我们正在尝试获取管理员权限，并且sudo命令
Now when I do that because we're trying to get administrator privileges and the sudo command is going
要求我们提供密码以输入我的密码，这是我通常用来登录的密码
to ask us for our password to enter my password which is the password I just use normally to log in
到下一台计算机。
to the next computer.
但是你知道，我们没有看到任何密码被输入。
But you know it's that we don't see any password being typed out.
这是一个内置在外壳中的安全功能，它阻止人们知道它的长度
Now this is a security feature that's built into the shell that stops people from knowing the length
您的密码。
of your passwords.
原因是，如果人们知道你密码的长度，破解密码就容易得多。
And the reason is that if people know the length of your password it makes cracking it so much easier.
所以不要担心你看不到任何反馈。
So don't worry that you don't see any feedback.
只需键入您的密码键入密码，当您按下该键时，外壳程序将接受该密码
Just type your password type the password is being accepted by the shell when you've done that press
输入，我们将看到shell在更新数据库时将暂停一段时间。
enter and we'll see that the shell will pause for a bit as it updates the database.
然后我们有一个shell提示符支持的广告，它让我们知道命令已经完成。
And then we have a shell prompt backed ad which lets us know that the command has completed.
现在我们已经更新了数据库，他们发现我的文件现在应该在数据库中了。
So now that we've updated our database they find me file should be in the database now.
那么让我们试着看看locate命令是否能找到它，让我们键入locate find me，找到那个文本。
So let's try and see if the locate command can find it let's type locate find me find me that text.
当我按Enter键时，您会看到，是的，这一次它确实找到了它，它告诉我们它在我们的桌面上
When I press Enter you'll see that yes it did find it this time it tells us it's on our desktop and
它叫“找到我，不是文本”，我们不一定要在桌面上。
it's called Find me not text and we don't have to be on the desktop.
我们可以在我们的Documents文件夹中，比方说，在我们的Documents文件夹中。
We could be in our let's say in our documents folder.
我们可以按Primack和DIRECTORY。
We can press Primack and directory.
我们在我们的文件中看到了这一点。
We see that in our documents.
但如果我真的找到了，找到任何类似的东西，你说它会出现冰沙家的奇怪的斜杠
But if I do locate find me anything like that and you say it comes up with slush home slashes the odd
劈开桌面劈开找我点xti，这样它就能告诉我们实际文件在哪里。
slash desktop slash find me dot XTi So it tells us where the where the actual file is.
现在，如果我们再来看一下数据库文件，让我们先回到桌面一分钟
Now if we take a look at the database file as well let's just head back to our desktop for a minute
让我们看一下数据库文件，因此我们使用带有大写S选项的LOCATE。
and let's take a look at the database file so we use locate with a capital S option.
我们可以看到，如果我在Dr.XTi之后将其保存为数据库，实际上这是改变的。
We can see that actually this is changed if I save that as data base after Dr. XTi.
这就是我们之前的数据库和之后的数据库，如果我在我们看到之前打开一个数据库
So here we are we've got a database before and database after if I open up a database before we see
我们有1608个目录14853个文件
that we have what sixteen thousand eight directories one four thousand eight hundred fifty three files
还有其他什么都行。
and whatever else.
现在，如果我之后试着打开，我们可以看到我们以前有过这个。
Now if I try to open up afterwards we can see here that we've got this before.
44,853个文件之后。
Forty four thousand eight hundred fifty three files afterwards.
少投了4,848票。
Under-vote four thousand eight hundred forty eight.
所以看起来有些文件实际上已经被删除了，或者来自系统7的某些文件具有哪七个
So it looks like some files have actually been deleted or something from the System 7 have what seven
2008年为5,000,000字节，之后为26字节。
million five in 2008 and 26 bytes afterwards.
是的，看起来好像自从我们上次更新数据库后，有些文件确实被删除了。
Yeah it actually looks as though since we last updated the database some files have indeed been deleted.
所以可能有一些临时文件在运行或类似的东西，但您可以看到
So maybe there was some temporary files in operation or something like that but you can see that the
当您更新数据库时，它的大小确实会更改。
size of the database does change when you update it.
好的。
OK.
但是如果我再做一次，如果我在两点之后做数据库，然后看一看，应该是绝对没有区别的
But if I do that again if I do database after two and take a look there should be absolutely no difference
在这两个之间。
between these two.
这是两天后的基数，我在两天后查看数据库，会发现它们实际上是完全相同的
So this is day base after and I look at database after two and will see that they are actually exactly
一样的。
the same.
好的。
OK.
因此，当您更新数据库时，它现在确实会更改，因为update D-B命令需要管理员
So when you update the database it does indeed change now because the update D-B command needs administrator
权限或root权限才能运行。
privileges or root privileges in order to run.
您可以看到LOCATE命令的EXISTING和FOLLOW选项存在的原因，这样您就可以了解为什么会有这些选项
You can see why the existing and follow options exist for the locate command so you can see why these
它们已存在，并遵循它们，因此当您等待管理员更新
ones exist existing and follow them so that when you're waiting for your administrator to update the
数据库即使您知道没有管理员，您作为普通用户仍可以继续工作
database you as a regular user can still get on with your work even if you know you don't have administrator
特权。
privileges.
您可以在管理员可能正在收发电子邮件的同时继续您的工作
You could just get on with your work while the administrator is you know probably catching up on emails
或者是一些很聪明的东西，对吧。
or something pretty clever right.
在过去的几个视频中，您已经了解了很多关于定位命令的知识。
So you've learnt a lot about the locate command in the past few videos.
因此，让我们快速回顾一下您所学的内容，以确保您掌握了全部内容。
So let's just take a quick recap of what you've learned to make sure that you've got it all.
首先，定位命令搜索是存储在您的计算机上的前四个数据库
First of all the locate command search is a database that stored on your computer for the first four
与您给出的模式匹配的文件会返回一个结果列表，使用数据库是非常重要的
files matching the pattern that you give it returns a list of results and using a database is a very
快速搜索方法，但它需要更新数据库才能为您提供完整的
fast method of searching but it requires that the database be updated in order to give you a complete
和正确的结果列表。
and correct list of results.
现在，您可以使用的现有和跟随选项从定位来保护自己免受错误的影响
Now you can protect yourself against errors using the existing and follow options for the from the locate
指挥部。
command.
但这并不是最好的解决方案，最好的做法就是使用
But that's not really the best solution the best thing to do is just to update the database using the
更新数据库命令。
update DB command.
但这也是每天自动完成的。
But this is done automatically daily as well.
现在，要做到这一点，它确实需要管理权限或超级权限
Now in order to do that it does require administrative administrative privileges or privileges or super
用户特权，随便你怎么称呼它。
user privileges whatever you want to call it.
因此，您需要使用sudo命令sudo命令才能实际获得这些权限。
And therefore you need to use the sudo command the sudo command in order to actually gain those privileges.
输入您的密码，然后以管理员身份运行该命令。
Enter your password and then the command is ran as the administrator.
因此，为了更新库，您不需要只键入update debug，您可以键入sudo update dbi输入您
So in order to update that base you don't just type update debug you type sudo update DBI enter your
密码，则数据库已更新，然后您可以从该点开始使用LOCATE命令
password and then the database is up dated and then you can use the locate command from that point on
并且知道您的结果将是100%正确和最新的。
and know that your results will be 100 percent correct and up to date.
所以Lowkey是一个非常有用的命令，我一直在使用它。
So Lowkey is a fantastically useful command and I use it all the time.
它使用起来真的很快，但是还有另一个不需要数据库的命令，它实际上可以
It's really quick to use but there's another command that doesn't require a database and it can actually
变得更加强大。
be way way more powerful.
它被称为“查找”命令，我们将在下一个视频中介绍这一点。
It's called Find command and we'll be covering that in the next video.
所以这真是令人惊叹。
So it's amazing.
它真的很酷，你可以用它以一种平静的方式做如此强大的事情来展示给你。
It really really is cool you can do such powerful things with it in a calm way to show you.
所以对于所有这些好东西。
So for all that good stuff.
我将在下一个视频中见到你。
I'll see you in the next video.